So now let's add the second objective so your second objective can be anything okay
you can go ahead and create your own story that for example the player will first find
a con and then there will be some kind of a bot somewhere in the environment and for the
bot the player must find for example pat roll or guess inside this building
okay and then you can put the key in here somewhere for example instead of a
key I have I will just add another rifle so in items weapons cons I'm going to
add this rifle okay but for example this will be the key of the board or a
guess can for the board okay this can be your second objective so I'm just
going to put this rifle in here right that okay and I'm gonna add teeth light
okay this light right there so that the player can see where the rifle is
let me minimize that so let this light and move it to this side okay this
will be our objective to area so I'm just gonna add this in the player
related okay and now closer to this rifle so let me over a player related select
this ump create a empty game object in the Android and drop it outside over this
will be our objective to okay this is the objective to let's add a box
color to this okay there it is the box color maybe it is triggered and add the
objective to the script to it and drag and drop the manager in there so
this will be our objective to now let's type the objective to in the game
manager so okay let's first of all objective one trigger right there and
then now let's add the second objective the second objective will be
find ump rifle you are second objective if you are using some other kind of story
your second objective will be find and gas can something like that okay but
mine is find ump or killing zombies faster all right and in the objective
trigger I'm gonna try and drop my second trigger okay so this will update the
second objective now I'm gonna just make my third objective the final one
which will be scape so a player will escape in some kind of vehicle okay this
is one vehicle right here but my vehicle will be standing right here okay
in flutter grounds pre-fabs then in pre-fabs we have props right here okay so
I'm just gonna add this car right here and this car has this material okay
so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna make the player escape in this car okay you
can add some other carbird for now I'm just gonna use this one so I'm just
gonna move this to the player related and in here I'm gonna quit empty came
object which will be used as a trigger okay I'm gonna name this as O3
add our box color to it there it is that's now resize this box color and when
the player reaches this bridge right here the player is just this point the
objective will be passed okay so to this one add the objective trigger right
there try and rotate manager in there then click on the manager and the third
objective no escape using cheap over into this try and rotate third objective right there and that will be it
objectives okay so now if we go ahead and play the game but actually before playing
the game click on edit project settings and in the project settings if you click
on player and then in the other settings make sure that you scroll down and
right here change the effective input handling from input system package new to
both and what this will do is this will restart the project okay once it is
restart now it is set to both we can now go ahead and play the game cave in the
game start if you press the tab button now as you can see it shows the first
objective which is find something for protection from zombies all right
then you can see it shows that for five seconds and then it disappear by it so
now if you go ahead and find something which is right here if you now check it is
still find something now if you pick this up now it is showing the next
objective which is find UMP for killing zombies faster so now we will kill
zombies right here and then go towards the second objective and complete
that but for now as you can see we don't have any zombies which we can spawn
so in the next video I'm going to show you how you can spawn zombies between
different type of objectives okay so for that see you guys in the next one